<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>A RimWorld of Magic</name>
	<author>Torann</author>
	<targetVersion>0.18.0</targetVersion>
	<description>Version 1.9.9.0
    This mod adds magic and class abilities to RimWorld.
	
Specially gifted pawns can find and use assortment of arcane scripts that bestow them with special abilities.  Most abilities
are combat related, though all classes possess limited skills to assist both on and off the battlefield.
	
Abilities are unique to each class, with each class specializing in specific roles:

Fire mage: highly destructive but difficult to control and has a tendency to start fires.

Ice mage: though not directly powerful, the ice mage is adept at decreasing the enemies ability to move and fight.

Lightning mage: summons deadly weather conditions at target areas, but its random nature produces unpredictable results.

Arcane mage: master of space and utility; has limited combat abilities but, with some improvisation, can control any fight.

Summoner: brings forth powerful, tactical defenses to protect the colony. Can summon mighty elementals and helpful minions.

Druid: a utility class that can improve the health of colonists or cause maladies on enemies; has some control over animal kind.

Necromancer: evil sorcerers with the intent of enslaving all creatures to do their bidding; manipulates forces of life and death

Paladin: excellent front line fighter that has the ability to close with, disrupt, and destroy enemy formations.

Priest: support class dedicated to the health and well-being of the colony.

Bard: expert in social interaction and inspiring other colonists.

Gladiator: versatile close combat specialist that thrives in the thick of battle.

Sniper: long range, small arms expert - excels at precision strikes that exploit enemy weaknesses.

Bladedancer: close range glass cannon, excels at hit and run tactics and rapid assaults

Ranger: survivalist and stalwart defender, the ranger enlists the aid of animal kin to defend the colony
	</description>
</ModMetaData>