<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	
	<!--===================== Concepts about magic taught through the learning readout, when opportunities arise ===================-->

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>TM_Portals</defName>
		<label>Using portals</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Magical portals representation the height of magical power.  There are a few things you should know about using portals:

1. Only an Arcane mage trained in Gateway magic can activate a portal.
 a. The option to activate a portal only appears when the Arcane mage has enough mana (70%) for activation.
 b. When the Arcane mage activates the portal, it will move the selection menu to the world map - only a map actively occupied by colonists can be selected.
 c. Activation will drain the mage for a brief time, so choose your destination with care.
 
2. Once activated, any mage can charge the portal.
 a. The options to use (walk through) a portal or send items through the portal only appear when the portal has enough arcane energy stored to perform the action.
 b. Only one pawn at a time may use the portal; each pawn drains the portal by 5% of its maximum energy.
 c. All items are transmitted simultaneously; the cost to transfer items through a portal is 10% of its maximum energy.
 
3. Any pawn can use the portal.

4. Only mages can direct items through the portal.

5. Only mages can deactivate the portal.

6. When a portal deactivates, it will retain the arcane power stored until the portal is reactivated.
Portals must be deactivated before they can be reactivated and assigned a new destination.

7. Protect your portal - it is fragile, expensive, and stores a massive amount of energy...
</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
		  
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>
	
		<ConceptDef>
		<defName>TM_Encanting</defName>
		<label>Enchanting</label>
		<priority>51</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>False</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Enchanting offers mages the ability to further refine and empower their abilities.  There are a few things you should know about enchanting:

1. Only mages can enchant!  The process of enchanting requires mana, so mundane pawns will be unable to equip an enchanting stone.
 
2. To enchant an item, your colony must complete the following prerequisites:
 a. Research the gemcutting workbench in the research menu, under the Magic tab
 b. Construct the workbench
 c. Acquire sufficient raw magicyte to form an enchanting stone.
 d. Raw magicitye can be found in any mineable stone, each mining strike has a chance to uncover raw magicyte. Any type of pawn can find raw magicyte.
 e. Using the gemcutting bench, form an enchanting stone. Any pawn can work the gemcutting workbench.
 
3. Once you've crafted an enchanting gem of your choice, you will need a mage to perform the enchantment.
 a. With a mage selected, right click on the enchanting gem and select the option to equip the gem for enchanting
 b. Select any apparel or weapon to receive the enchantment, and place the item on the ground. It's recommended to make sure the itemizedlist
 is not stacked with any other item so that the enchantment affects the desired item
 c. To perform the enchantment, with the mage holding the enchantment gem selected, right click on the item to be enchanted. If the mage does
 not have enough mana, the menu to perform the enchantment will be unselectable
 d. When the criteria to perform the enchantment is met, the menu option becomes available and your mage will move to, and enchant, the selected
 item
</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
		  
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

			<ConceptDef>
		<defName>TM_EncantingII</defName>
		<label>Enchanting II</label>
		<priority>52</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>False</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Enchanting: Part II
		
4. Enchantments are permanent and each item may hold one enchantment of each type.  New enchantments of the same type will replace the existing 
enchantment.  Enchanting an item does not increase the value of the item.  Enchanting an item consumes the enchanting gemstone.  There is
currently no way to extract an enchantment from an item.

5. Raw magicyte (and refined gemstones) may also be purchased from select vendors. The process of deep ore mining, unfortunately, filters out
the chance to acquire raw magicyte in this manner. Users of the "quarry" can add magicyte to the extracted minerals, the recommended value is 0.4%
 
6. Mundane pawns will not gain any benefit from equipping an enchanted item.

7. If you wish to drop an enchanting stone - with the mage holding the enchanting gem, right click on any open square and select the menu option
to drop the gem.

8. Item enchantments can be viewed on individual gear by selecting the item on the ground and using the "Enchanted" tab. The collective Enchantments 
affecting a single pawn can be seen in the health tab.		
</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
		  
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>
</Defs>


