<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>A RimWorld Of Magic</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>ARimWorldOfMagic</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=37161.0</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New Class: Warlock/Succubus - gaining their power through a demonic contract, this class is gender specific where each gender shares common powers but are also uniquely diverse in both roles and application of their powers.
*Soul Bond - form a contract with another colonist that allows the class to gain additional power; this weakens the capacity of the bonded pawn but eases the burden of their reality...
>>Forming a soul bond grants a unique link between the bonded pawn and the warlock or succubus that allows them to travel to, or summon, the bonded pawn across vast distances
*Shadow Bolt - launch a bolt of blackest shadow to consume the energy of everything along its path
*Dominate - an infectious calamity of nightmares and fears that erodes the sanity of its victims
*(Warlock) Repulsion - detonate a burst of raw energy that repels any nearby pawns
*(Succubus) Attraction - create an inescapable pit of darkness that draws victims into the center and surrounds them in clinging shadows
*(Warlock - Master) Psychic Shock - release all mental barriers and emit a powerful psychic shockwave to dominate the minds of nearby pawns
*(Succubus - Master) Scorn - reveal your true nature and crush your opponents in cascading wrath

- Several compatibility patches have been added for the Lord of the Rims mods that was preventing summoned creatures from spawning.

- (Bug fixes) Blink no longer charges double the stated casting cost; you can no longer raise summoned/elemental creatures as undead; undead should no longer be sellable; Undead animals will no longer procreate; Necromancer/Lich will now correctly write their Unfinished Arcane Tomes.
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_2_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.2.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- Psychic Sensitivity now affects how powerful, and susceptible, a pawn is to magic.
- The Warlock and Succubus classes will exhibit unique social behaviors.  The Succubus is a bit more friendly and the Warlock may cause emotions to 'bleed' from, or to, other pawns via psychic empathy.
- A hidden combination ability has been added for Warlock and Succubus; not for the faint of heart.
- The arcane mine now has a small proximity detection and should be much more responsive to enemies passing nearby.
- The Bard class has been added to the random class pool.
- Psychic Shock will only damage the mind of an enemy once, but applies a stronger stun to enemies and a weaker stun to friendlies.
- Mod default settings for Magicyte rarity have been increased, in addition, most trader types will carry small amounts of magicyte for purchase (at higher costs than arcane vendors).
- Enchanting gem recipe's have been changed to only require a flat raw magicyte amount. This will reduce the overall time and cost to craft higher tier gems.
- Eye of the Storm master spell will discharge when it reaches its destination instead of just disappearing.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_2_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.2.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New Class: Psionic - pawns influenced by increased sensitivity or events of psychic power and being physically adept allows access to a combat class that blends mental and physical strength to overcome challenges.

Psionics gain access to a unique mechanic called psionic energy; the balanced use of physical and psionic energy produces the most effective results for a psionic.

*Psionic Augmentation - a psionic is most efficient when combining physical and mental strength; psionic augmentation is the application of psionic energy into living tissue and practices in three major ways:
>Movement - infusing psionic energy into the core and legs the psionic is able to move at incredible speeds
>Manipulation - applying psionic energy into hands and arms increases manipulation speed and power
>Mind - exerts raw psionic power to strike at foes from a distance
*Psionic blast - launch a bolt of explosive energy; higher levels of psionic energy can produce multiple bolts
*Psionic dash - a physical burst of energy propelled by psionic energy causes the psionic to move at devastating speeds over a short distance
*Psionic storm - harnesses all reserves of psionic energy in a spectacular display of power
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
		<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_2_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.2.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
** New gizmo (icon) added for all classes to show their energy (mana, stamina, psionic energy) status.  Shows only when a single pawn is selected.  This gizmo is enabled by default but can be disabled in the mod options.

Psionic changes: 
	Added a toggle button to enable or disable the use of "augmentation" abilities for a psionic
	Psionics will no longer use augmented dash in combat if using a ranged weapon
	Psionics will return to their starting position after using psionic storm
	Psionic blast has a reduced stamina cost / Psionic dash has an increased stamina cost

Geomancer changes:
	Stoneskin charges reduced from 6,8,9,10 -> 4,5,6,7
	Stoneskin will be reapplied on a pawn if they already have stoneskin but the number of charges is less than the number the casting geomancer can apply and will be dispelled if the charges are equal or greater
	
Mana drain: maximum duration has been reduced by 5 game hrs
Mana sickness: mages will recover from mana sickness 40% faster

Bug fixes: 
	Attempting to see what a trader wants to buy no longer generates an error
	Minions will no longer "divide by zero" for caravan food supplies
	Dismissing a minion that's part of a caravan will remove the minion from the caravan (instantly)
	Sending a minion on a caravan will no longer remove it from the casters list of minions
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
			<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_2_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.2.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
** New feature: Auto-casting - many basic spells or skills can now be enabled for automatic use.  There are a few things you should know:
- Abilities with autocast will have a checkbox at the top right of the ability icon; right click the ability icon to toggle the feature.
- There are two separate routines for drafted and undrafted.  Some spells, like magic combat spells, will only autocast while drafted.
- The only offensive abilities that will be used while undrafted are Ranger "Arrow Storm" and Sniper "Headshot" - and only when hunting.
- Autocast settings can be found in the mod options, and can be turned off globally if desired or for performance reasons.
- Outside of combat and hunting, autocast abilities will only target human colonists.
- Enabling autocast does not prevent normal use of abilities.
	
** New feature: Class options - within the mod settings there is a button for "Class Options" that will allow you to disable certain classes from being generated during gameplay.
- This does not remove traits from the database.  Disabled class traits will never be assigned during normal gameplay but use of mods like EdB Prepare Carefully or any mod that ignores trait commonality settings, will still show the trait.
- This feature should not be used in the middle of a game, only apply changes before starting a new game.
	
* New weapons - Elephant bow and Elephant spear - these weapons are intended to provide extra benefit to fighter classes at mid-tier (industrial equivalent) and have minor enchantments, similar to wands for mages.

Bug fixes: 
Geomancer "Encase" has been recoded to prevent "terrain swapping" and accidental destruction of a building if the swapped terrain type didn't support the building
Fixed an issue where several spells that should ignore terrain were 'hitting' objects or terrain prior to reaching their designated targets
Equipment (apparel) should now show their enchantments in the gear tab, along with weapons
Fixed an issue where Bards performing the "entertain" job wouldn't properly reserve their targets
Fixed a bug with Warlock "Empathy Bleed" that would attempt to feel empathy for colony pets
Warlock/Succubus can no longer soulbond themselves

		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_2_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.2.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
** New class: Technomancer - the technomancer combines technology and the arcane power as the basis for their abilities. They are unique in that they can select one (and only one) of three primary paths: offense, defense, and support
- Offensive Path: by using an existing, mechanical weapon as a blueprint, the technomancer can design a modified version of that weapon and mold it out of mana; the combination of this improved weapon system, nanites that increase their combat abilites, and projectiles infused with elemental properties makes the offensive technomancer a formidable option
- Defensive Path: the Mark-IV weapon system was a prototype that failed due to a lack of sustainable energy; technomancers use their own mana as a means to fuel this weapon system, and are able to effectively deploy and operate it as a powerful, manned turret
- Support Path: support technomancers prefer to craft an independent and autonomous AI to assist them in many tasks; this "techno-bit" is able to accelerate the work speed of many projects, can repair almost any mechanical system, and even has some combat abilities
In addition to the primary paths, all technomancers have access to several core, class abilities:
- Overdrive: bypasses safety features or increases power of generators, turrets, and robotic AI to drastically improve their output capacity for a short period but can cause stress and damage the targeted system
- Sabotage: like overdrive, it can target many different powered, computer, or mechanical systems to cause everything from minor to catastrophic failure of all vulnerable systems in a small area
- Kinetic Shield: surrounds the target with a shield able to deflect projectiles; the shields power determines the limit of kinetic energy that can be deflected - high powered rounds can penetrate low powered kinetic shields
- Orbital Strike; hacks into orbital bombardment satellites to input target coordinates, can take some time to align and launch the attack but packs a punch when it hits

** New Features:
Purify can be selected for Autocast
	
** Tweaks:
Autocast blink and phase strike XP gain has been reduced
Mana potion recipe for the gemcrafting replaces Go-Juice with other, less technological, ingredients
Autocast will not select targets out of line of sight - this was causing some abilities to move the casting pawn into a position it could see the target; this does not affect abilities that do not require line of sight
Sentinels will now activate on manhunter animals
Faceless ability "possess" can be resisted with above average values of consciousness and/or psychic sensitivity
Arcane cooler, heater, and power node have been changed to sustained abilities

Bug fixes:
Pawns of non-standard sizes will only be drawn as their intended sizes
Carrying capacity has been fixed for several traits that increased or decreased this state
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	
</Defs>