<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>A RimWorld Of Magic</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>ARimWorldOfMagic</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=37161.0</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
		<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.8</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- A RimWorld of Magic has undergone a balance update in order to adjust for mod updates and features that have been added over time. Descriptions have also been updated to adjust for the changes and for clarity.

- The ability Cleave (Gladiator) has been reworked and will trigger automatically when using a melee weapon, the chance depends on the weight of the weapon.

- The ability Regrow Limb (Druid) has been renamed to Regrowth and can regrow the majority of body parts. This ability no longer requires 2 mana potions.

- A mod setting has been added that will allow you to hide abilities when multiple pawns are selected. This hides all abilities not part of the vanilla command buttons, even those buttons are not part of this mod.

- Added compatibility updates for Combat Extended, No Water No Life, and Call of Cthulhu mods.
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_9</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.9</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- A Chinese translation has been added to the mod - big thanks to KuanKuan!

- The Elemental Rift event has undergone some changes.  When a rift occurs, the element type is determined and will remain that type for the remainder of the event.  Each element type is accompanied by a unique set of atmospheric conditions that will present additional challenges to the colony.

- Magicyte can now be extracted from dead elementals at the butchery table.

- The exact mana gain can now be seen under the Magic tab; hovering over the value will provide a tooltip showing contributors to the amount.

- Enchantments are now shown under an item in the gear/inventory tab; this should make it much easier to find equipped items that have enchantments. The characters shown in parenthesis are a quick code for the types of enchantments affecting the item; mousing over the text will also bring up a tooltip that shows the exact enchantments.

- Research tiers have been adjusted slightly to split projects into either neolithic or medieval; net research costs are approximately the same.

- Casting graphics have been added to help identify friendly and enemy pawns that are casting a spell.

- Other miscellaneous updates include improvements for Spell Mending, thrumbo horns have been added as a resource requirement for the thrumbo axe, jade has been added to arcane traders, undead can no longer be captured and more!
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New Class: Faceless (might) - faceless excel at manipulation, perception, and deception; through their cunning tactics, they can take the strength of another and make it their own. 
*Deception - exploiting knowledge of how other pawns perceive things, the faceless are able to blend into the canopy, becoming just another harmless object to an observer, making themselves all but invisible. Performing hostile actions will break the deception.
*Mimic - creates an imitation of a fighter or mage skill; can be used on enemy or friendly pawns alike to acquire a one-time-use ability.
*Reversal - reverses the kinetic energy of projectile and melee attacks back towards the attacker for a short time
*Transpose - the faceless takes the place of another pawn and forces the other pawn to take its place
*Possess - confuses the mind of a target pawn to gain (limited) control over their body; if used on a willing host, the faceless enhances physical capability of the host
 
- New mod options have been added to allow you to mark enemy fighter classes; another new option allows friendly pawns (mages and fighters) to also be marked.

- Global skills Spirit (mage) and Endurance (fighter) now give 4% boost to their respective resource pool maximum levels (was 2%).
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New Class: Warlock/Succubus - gaining their power through a demonic contract, this class is gender specific where each gender shares common powers but are also uniquely diverse in both roles and application of their powers.
*Soul Bond - form a contract with another colonist that allows the class to gain additional power; this weakens the capacity of the bonded pawn but eases the burden of their reality...
>>Forming a soul bond grants a unique link between the bonded pawn and the warlock or succubus that allows them to travel to, or summon, the bonded pawn across vast distances
*Shadow Bolt - launch a bolt of blackest shadow to consume the energy of everything along its path
*Dominate - an infectious calamity of nightmares and fears that erodes the sanity of its victims
*(Warlock) Repulsion - detonate a burst of raw energy that repels any nearby pawns
*(Succubus) Attraction - create an inescapable pit of darkness that draws victims into the center and surrounds them in clinging shadows
*(Warlock - Master) Psychic Shock - release all mental barriers and emit a powerful psychic shockwave to dominate the minds of nearby pawns
*(Succubus - Master) Scorn - reveal your true nature and crush your opponents in cascading wrath

- Several compatibility patches have been added for the Lord of the Rims mods that was preventing summoned creatures from spawning.

- (Bug fixes) Blink no longer charges double the stated casting cost; you can no longer raise summoned/elemental creatures as undead; undead should no longer be sellable; Undead animals will no longer procreate; Necromancer/Lich will now correctly write their Unfinished Arcane Tomes.
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_2_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.2.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- Psychic Sensitivity now affects how powerful, and susceptible, a pawn is to magic.
- The Warlock and Succubus classes will exhibit unique social behaviors.  The Succubus is a bit more friendly and the Warlock may cause emotions to 'bleed' from, or to, other pawns via psychic empathy.
- A hidden combination ability has been added for Warlock and Succubus; not for the faint of heart.
- The arcane mine now has a small proximity detection and should be much more responsive to enemies passing nearby.
- The Bard class has been added to the random class pool.
- Psychic Shock will only damage the mind of an enemy once, but applies a stronger stun to enemies and a weaker stun to friendlies.
- Mod default settings for Magicyte rarity have been increased, in addition, most trader types will carry small amounts of magicyte for purchase (at higher costs than arcane vendors).
- Enchanting gem recipe's have been changed to only require a flat raw magicyte amount. This will reduce the overall time and cost to craft higher tier gems.
- Eye of the Storm master spell will discharge when it reaches its destination instead of just disappearing.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	
</Defs>