<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>A RimWorld Of Magic</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>ARimWorldOfMagic</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=37161.0</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- Seven new fighter class specific abilities have been added. These abilities are 'sustained' meaning they require a set amount of stamina to maintain the ability.
The sustainment cost is subtracted from the users maximum stamina. These skills can be toggled on and off as desired, some of these skills have additional costs or side effects to maintain.
Skills:
Sprint - increase movement rate but quickly exhausts the user (Gladiator class can improve this skill through training)
Gear Repair - fighter classes rely on their equipment and take the initiative to maintain and repair equipped apparel and weapons
Inner Healing - focuses physical energy to slowly heal injuries, some physical capacities are reduced while this skill is active
Heavy Blow - increase melee damage multiplier by 20%
Strong Back - dedicates stamina to increase carrying and inventory capacity, slightly increases exhaustion
Thick Skin - gains bonuses to armor class and temperature thresholds
Fighters Focus - dedicates physical energy to focus on, and overcome, mental and physical thresholds

- Fighter skills that applied passive boosts or trait increases now take effect automatically, and apply upgrades automatically.  The ability buttons for these skills will not be visible.

- Fighters and Mages have each gained a new global skill that increases their respective stamina and mana capacities.

- Inherited abilities for Summon Minion and Raise Undead have been added to improve Undead and Minion management. These skills become available automatically when a mage is supporting one or more of these creatures.
No additional scrolls or training is required to learn these skills.

- A new standalone mage spell has been added: Arcane Power Node - generates a small amount of power for several days. 
Existing abilities "Moisturize Ground" and "Dry Ground" now effect a 3x3 square; mana costs were appropriately increased.
The "Rainmaker" ability can now be used to stop rain or snow.

- Bug fix - several fighter skills were not triggering a hostile response, they are now.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- Fixes issues with elemental rift not spawning elementals and causing game crashes when the event ends.  Elemental rifts will now award gems at the end of the event.

- Fixes Arcane power nodes where the duration is correctly applied.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- Special thanks to mod contributor Sihv for the following: new additions for scribing of arcane books and scrolls has been added, these items can be researched and constructed using the scribing table.

- New research and crafting recipes have been added to allow the construction of powerful Gems of Insight that allow mundane pawns to learn the Gifted or Physical Prodigy traits.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
		<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New magical armor and weapons have been added. These items can be researched in the magic research tab and become available starting with completion of Arcane Apparel research.  These items provide augmented magical stats and unique enchantments and are designed for magic users.  Once researched, they can be crafted at standard crafting spots and tailoring and smithing benches.

- Recipe costs and market value for enchanted gems and scrolls has been reduced.

- Two new enchantments have been added: arcane damage and arcane resistance. 
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- The Paladin, Necromancer, and Summoner master spells have been added:

Paladin - Holy Wrath: calls or a hammers of light to smash upon the land

Necromancer - Lich Form: the necromancer steps further along the path of the dark mage by becoming an undead; by doing so, they lose interest in almost all mundane tasks but gain the Death Bolt and Flight powers
The necromancer "Death Mark" power has been reworked. It now functions as a curse that will slow the attack speed of any enemy affected. The fear that Death Mark induces also becomes a source of power that the lich will use to empower Death Bolt
Undead workspeeds have been reduced but will gain the benefits of the "Hastened Undead" skill towards global work speed

Summoner - Summon Poppi: a curious creature that fights more ferociously than any other creature on the rim, a true demon in disguise

- New stand-alone spell "Sun Light" - creates a node of light powerful enough to grow plants but places a continuous demand on the mage sustaining the light.

- Ranger pets now require a cost to maintain; rangers will be more sensitive to the loss of their bonded companions.

- Several new weapons to include the Thrumbo Axe, which is powerful enough to perform cleaving blows, and the Staff of the Defender that enables any mage to form temporary arcane barriers
	
- Special thanks to contributor Angry Wizard for improving many of the UI icons and Dianne for the Poppi graphics!
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.7</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New Class: Bard (magic) - the bard utilizes a variety of social interaction and abilities to improve the morale and efficiency of other colonists. The bard is naturally skilled at social activities to include diplomacy, trade, and negotiations.
Abilities:
*Entertain - uses charm, wit, and humor to improve the mood of other colonists. This is a new social interaction (like chit chat or deep talk) that is always active (once learned) and is unique to the bard class. In addition, the bard may activate the 'entertain' ability to identify other colonists that are reaching their breaking points and attempt to improve their mood.
*Inspire - another ability of the bard that works in the background (once learned) and will attempt to inspire nearby colonists.
*Lullaby - the bard plays an enchanting lullaby that washes away consciousness of any pawns in the affected area.
*Battle Hymn (master) - plays an exhilarating battle song that increases the fighting spirit of any nearby pawns. The effects of Battle Hymn build over time.

- Three new stand-alone spells:
*Cauterize Wounds (fire mage) - instantly cleans and tends any wounds on the target, but has a chance to cause burn scars.
*Spell Mending (any mage) - Combines arcane power of the mage and physical energy of the target to repair the equipment worn by the target.
*Fertile Lands (druid) - blesses a large area of land with the power of the druids that increases the growth rate of any plants within the area by 200%. This spell is maintained by the druid, and reduces mana regeneration by 40%.

- As part of the Bard update, 6 new inspirations have been added: Learning (introspection), Social (outgoing), Farming, Mining, and two special inspirations unique to mage and fighter classes.

- Mages that share a positive social standing can now exchange arcane knowledge as part of a Mentor/Student interaction. This allows less experienced mages to learn from those more experienced int he magical arts. 
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
		<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.8</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- A RimWorld of Magic has undergone a balance update in order to adjust for mod updates and features that have been added over time. Descriptions have also been updated to adjust for the changes and for clarity.

- The ability Cleave (Gladiator) has been reworked and will trigger automatically when using a melee weapon, the chance depends on the weight of the weapon.

- The ability Regrow Limb (Druid) has been renamed to Regrowth and can regrow the majority of body parts. This ability no longer requires 2 mana potions.

- A mod setting has been added that will allow you to hide abilities when multiple pawns are selected. This hides all abilities not part of the vanilla command buttons, even those buttons are not part of this mod.

- Added compatibility updates for Combat Extended, No Water No Life, and Call of Cthulhu mods.
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	
</Defs>