<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>A RimWorld Of Magic</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>ARimWorldOfMagic</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=37161.0</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- The Paladin, Necromancer, and Summoner master spells have been added:

Paladin - Holy Wrath: calls or a hammers of light to smash upon the land

Necromancer - Lich Form: the necromancer steps further along the path of the dark mage by becoming an undead; by doing so, they lose interest in almost all mundane tasks but gain the Death Bolt and Flight powers
The necromancer "Death Mark" power has been reworked. It now functions as a curse that will slow the attack speed of any enemy affected. The fear that Death Mark induces also becomes a source of power that the lich will use to empower Death Bolt
Undead workspeeds have been reduced but will gain the benefits of the "Hastened Undead" skill towards global work speed

Summoner - Summon Poppi: a curious creature that fights more ferociously than any other creature on the rim, a true demon in disguise

- New stand-alone spell "Sun Light" - creates a node of light powerful enough to grow plants but places a continuous demand on the mage sustaining the light.

- Ranger pets now require a cost to maintain; rangers will be more sensitive to the loss of their bonded companions.

- Several new weapons to include the Thrumbo Axe, which is powerful enough to perform cleaving blows, and the Staff of the Defender that enables any mage to form temporary arcane barriers
	
- Special thanks to contributor Angry Wizard for improving many of the UI icons and Dianne for the Poppi graphics!
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.7</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New Class: Bard (magic) - the bard utilizes a variety of social interaction and abilities to improve the morale and efficiency of other colonists. The bard is naturally skilled at social activities to include diplomacy, trade, and negotiations.
Abilities:
*Entertain - uses charm, wit, and humor to improve the mood of other colonists. This is a new social interaction (like chit chat or deep talk) that is always active (once learned) and is unique to the bard class. In addition, the bard may activate the 'entertain' ability to identify other colonists that are reaching their breaking points and attempt to improve their mood.
*Inspire - another ability of the bard that works in the background (once learned) and will attempt to inspire nearby colonists.
*Lullaby - the bard plays an enchanting lullaby that washes away consciousness of any pawns in the affected area.
*Battle Hymn (master) - plays an exhilarating battle song that increases the fighting spirit of any nearby pawns. The effects of Battle Hymn build over time.

- Three new stand-alone spells:
*Cauterize Wounds (fire mage) - instantly cleans and tends any wounds on the target, but has a chance to cause burn scars.
*Spell Mending (any mage) - Combines arcane power of the mage and physical energy of the target to repair the equipment worn by the target.
*Fertile Lands (druid) - blesses a large area of land with the power of the druids that increases the growth rate of any plants within the area by 200%. This spell is maintained by the druid, and reduces mana regeneration by 40%.

- As part of the Bard update, 6 new inspirations have been added: Learning (introspection), Social (outgoing), Farming, Mining, and two special inspirations unique to mage and fighter classes.

- Mages that share a positive social standing can now exchange arcane knowledge as part of a Mentor/Student interaction. This allows less experienced mages to learn from those more experienced int he magical arts. 
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
		<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.8</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- A RimWorld of Magic has undergone a balance update in order to adjust for mod updates and features that have been added over time. Descriptions have also been updated to adjust for the changes and for clarity.

- The ability Cleave (Gladiator) has been reworked and will trigger automatically when using a melee weapon, the chance depends on the weight of the weapon.

- The ability Regrow Limb (Druid) has been renamed to Regrowth and can regrow the majority of body parts. This ability no longer requires 2 mana potions.

- A mod setting has been added that will allow you to hide abilities when multiple pawns are selected. This hides all abilities not part of the vanilla command buttons, even those buttons are not part of this mod.

- Added compatibility updates for Combat Extended, No Water No Life, and Call of Cthulhu mods.
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_1_9_9</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.9</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- A Chinese translation has been added to the mod - big thanks to KuanKuan!

- The Elemental Rift event has undergone some changes.  When a rift occurs, the element type is determined and will remain that type for the remainder of the event.  Each element type is accompanied by a unique set of atmospheric conditions that will present additional challenges to the colony.

- Magicyte can now be extracted from dead elementals at the butchery table.

- The exact mana gain can now be seen under the Magic tab; hovering over the value will provide a tooltip showing contributors to the amount.

- Enchantments are now shown under an item in the gear/inventory tab; this should make it much easier to find equipped items that have enchantments. The characters shown in parenthesis are a quick code for the types of enchantments affecting the item; mousing over the text will also bring up a tooltip that shows the exact enchantments.

- Research tiers have been adjusted slightly to split projects into either neolithic or medieval; net research costs are approximately the same.

- Casting graphics have been added to help identify friendly and enemy pawns that are casting a spell.

- Other miscellaneous updates include improvements for Spell Mending, thrumbo horns have been added as a resource requirement for the thrumbo axe, jade has been added to arcane traders, undead can no longer be captured and more!
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New Class: Faceless (might) - faceless excel at manipulation, perception, and deception; through their cunning tactics, they can take the strength of another and make it their own. 
*Deception - exploiting knowledge of how other pawns perceive things, the faceless are able to blend into the canopy, becoming just another harmless object to an observer, making themselves all but invisible. Performing hostile actions will break the deception.
*Mimic - creates an imitation of a fighter or mage skill; can be used on enemy or friendly pawns alike to acquire a one-time-use ability.
*Reversal - reverses the kinetic energy of projectile and melee attacks back towards the attacker for a short time
*Transpose - the faceless takes the place of another pawn and forces the other pawn to take its place
*Possess - confuses the mind of a target pawn to gain (limited) control over their body; if used on a willing host, the faceless enhances physical capability of the host
 
- New mod options have been added to allow you to mark enemy fighter classes; another new option allows friendly pawns (mages and fighters) to also be marked.

- Global skills Spirit (mage) and Endurance (fighter) now give 4% boost to their respective resource pool maximum levels (was 2%).
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ARimWorldOfMagic_2_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- New Class: Warlock/Succubus - gaining their power through a demonic contract, this class is gender specific where each gender shares common powers but are also uniquely diverse in both roles and application of their powers.
*Soul Bond - form a contract with another colonist that allows the class to gain additional power; this weakens the capacity of the bonded pawn but eases the burden of their reality...
>>Forming a soul bond grants a unique link between the bonded pawn and the warlock or succubus that allows them to travel to, or summon, the bonded pawn across vast distances
*Shadow Bolt - launch a bolt of blackest shadow to consume the energy of everything along its path
*Dominate - an infectious calamity of nightmares and fears that erodes the sanity of its victims
*(Warlock) Repulsion - detonate a burst of raw energy that repels any nearby pawns
*(Succubus) Attraction - create an inescapable pit of darkness that draws victims into the center and surrounds them in clinging shadows
*(Warlock - Master) Psychic Shock - release all mental barriers and emit a powerful psychic shockwave to dominate the minds of nearby pawns
*(Succubus - Master) Scorn - reveal your true nature and crush your opponents in cascading wrath

- Several compatibility patches have been added for the Lord of the Rims mods that was preventing summoned creatures from spawning.

- (Bug fixes) Blink no longer charges double the stated casting cost; you can no longer raise summoned/elemental creatures as undead; undead should no longer be sellable; Undead animals will no longer procreate; Necromancer/Lich will now correctly write their Unfinished Arcane Tomes.
	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	
</Defs>