<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<TM_ReverseTime.label>Reverse Time</TM_ReverseTime.label>

	<TM_ReverseTime.description>Reverse Time applies a field around the target where all physical matter reverses its natural decay. Reversing the effects of time is more difficult - it requires more energy than accelerating time and can only be applied to a single target at a time.

When applied to inanimate objects, the effect is instant and will regenerate items and restore material to a previous state. Reverse Time can be used to restore rotting food, decaying equipment, and tainted material.

Living tissue will resist instant change and requires a more gradual approach. Any living pawn affected will have decreased movement and manipulation speed and their biological aging will reverse. This can remove many ailments that were caused recently as the tissue is restored to a state prior to the ailment; this includes wounds, diseases, and age related ailments that occurred within the window of time reversal.

Reverse Time can be dispelled by countering the effects with Accelerate Time.</TM_ReverseTime.description>

	<TM_ChronostaticField_I.label>Chronostatic Field (I)</TM_ChronostaticField_I.label>

	<TM_ChronostaticField_I.description>Chronostatic Field (also referred to as a time bubble) places all living creatures within the effected area out of phase with the flow of time. Interaction with affected creatures is impossible until they are returned to the natural flow of time.

Radius: 3.5
Range: 44
Cast time: .8s</TM_ChronostaticField_I.description>

	<TM_ChronostaticField.label>Chronostatic Field</TM_ChronostaticField.label>

	<TM_ChronostaticField.description>Chronostatic Field (also referred to as a time bubble) places all living creatures within the effected area out of phase with the flow of time. Interaction with affected creatures is impossible until they are returned to the natural flow of time.

Radius: 3
Range: 40
Cast time: 1s</TM_ChronostaticField.description>

	<TM_ChronostaticField_III.label>Chronostatic Field (III)</TM_ChronostaticField_III.label>

	<TM_ChronostaticField_III.description>Chronostatic Field (also referred to as a time bubble) places all living creatures within the effected area out of phase with the flow of time. Interaction with affected creatures is impossible until they are returned to the natural flow of time.

Radius: 4.5
Range: 50
Cast time: .5s</TM_ChronostaticField_III.description>

	<TM_AlterFate.label>Alter Fate</TM_AlterFate.label>

	<TM_AlterFate.description>Alter the flow of time to avoid predicted disasters. This ability relies on accurate Predictions to shape the future. Highly skilled chronomancers can revert environmental conditions even after they occur.
	
Alter Fate is most effective against environmental conditions. This ability can backfire, however, causing the event to change, become more severe, or trigger the infamous "butterfly effect."</TM_AlterFate.description>

	<TM_AccelerateTime.label>Accelerate Time</TM_AccelerateTime.label>

	<TM_AccelerateTime.description>Accelerate Time applies a field around the target where all physical matter rapidly ages.

When applied to inanimate objects, the effect is instant and will deteriorate items significantly; this can cause an item to disassemble into its base components. There is no area of effect for this function, only the object at the center will be affected.

Living tissue will resist instant change, and requires a more gradual approach. Any living pawn affected will have increased movement and manipulation speed. Neutral elements (plants) will experience rapid growth.

When use at a location or on a hostile enemy, all enemies in the area will be cursed with rapid aging. This will drain rest and energy from the target, accelerate other health conditions, and may inflict age related ailments.

When used on friendly pawns, there is no area of effect, only the primary target will be affected. The aging process for friendly pawns is much more gradual, and may be canceled by Reverse Time.</TM_AccelerateTime.description>

	<TM_ChronostaticField_II.label>Chronostatic Field (II)</TM_ChronostaticField_II.label>

	<TM_ChronostaticField_II.description>Chronostatic Field (also referred to as a time bubble) places all living creatures within the effected area out of phase with the flow of time. Interaction with affected creatures is impossible until they are returned to the natural flow of time.

Radius: 4
Range: 48
Cast time: .6s</TM_ChronostaticField_II.description>

	<TM_Prediction.label>Prediction</TM_Prediction.label>

	<TM_Prediction.description>Enables Prediction - a conscious effort dedicated to deciphering future events. Prediction has two components.
	
The first component is a self-awareness and intuition that makes the chronomancer uncannily difficult to harm, however, this splits the attention of the chronomancer and reduces their physical acuity and speed.

The second component focuses on the prediction of significant events. Indicators such as flight of birds, a cloud of dust, a sound in the wind are highlighted to the chronomancer and woven together into a tapestry depicting a possible future.

Neither method is infallible, but practice can improve the accuracy of prediction and reduce the focus required to sustain it.

This ability reduces mana regeneration by 50%.</TM_Prediction.description>

	<TM_Recall.label>Recall</TM_Recall.label>

	<TM_Recall.description>Returns the caster to a previous point in time. Cannot be used without an active time marker.</TM_Recall.description>

	<TM_TimeMark.label>Time Mark</TM_TimeMark.label>

	<TM_TimeMark.description>The chronomancer is able to capture their status at a specific point in time and return themselves to that point. This ability does not change time or affect anything else besides the chronomancer. The chronomancer will retain any memories they have at the time recall is activated; automated activation from a killing blow can inflict mental breaks since the chronomancer will remember their death.

Recall has a limited effective span (~1 day) before the time marker expires and must be re-applied. When the time marker is active, max MP is reduced by 40 mana and mana regeneration is decreased by 30%.

When set to autocast, the chronomancer will attempt to maintain a recall marker at all times - this does not affect activation triggers (downed/dead) which will always trigger if the skill is learned and time is marked.

To maintain physical cohesion during a recall, the caster will retain all conditions with permanence (missing or added body parts, permanent injuries).  All chronomancer spells are reset following a Recall except Recall itself.</TM_TimeMark.description>

</LanguageData>
