<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<TM_Entertain.label>Entertain</TM_Entertain.label>

	<TM_Entertain.description>Entertain fellow colonists using a variety of methods. This skill has two components, a passive skill and an active skill. The passive skill allows the bard to entertain other colonists in passing conversation.

This command toggles the active skill on or off.
	
Activating the ability casts a net over the colony and allows the bard to detect troubled pawns and attempt to entertain them. The bard will gain experience points as a mage when active entertaining is successful. Keeping this ability active reduces max mana by 30. The bard performs entertainment as a type of job, and will perform entertainment based on the priority of the "Warden" work type.</TM_Entertain.description>

	<TM_Inspire.label>Inspire</TM_Inspire.label>

	<TM_Inspire.description>The bard inspires other nearby pawns. This ability is always active.</TM_Inspire.description>

	<TM_Lullaby_II.label>Lullaby (II)</TM_Lullaby_II.label>

	<TM_Lullaby_II.description>Projects an emotionally soothing wave that washes away concerns and consciousness that can put any creatures in the target area to sleep.</TM_Lullaby_II.description>

	<TM_Lullaby_I.label>Lullaby (I)</TM_Lullaby_I.label>

	<TM_Lullaby_I.description>Projects an emotionally soothing wave that washes away concerns and consciousness that can put any creatures in the target area to sleep.</TM_Lullaby_I.description>

	<TM_Lullaby.label>Lullaby</TM_Lullaby.label>

	<TM_Lullaby.description>Projects an emotionally soothing wave that washes away concerns and consciousness that can put any creatures in the target area to sleep. Does not work on mechanoids.</TM_Lullaby.description>

	<TM_BattleHymn.label>Battle Hymn</TM_BattleHymn.label>

	<TM_BattleHymn.description>Play a rousing battle hymn to motivate and empower nearby allies. Each verse of the hymn adds to the effect and will further bolster the combat power of allies. Every verse consumes 9% additional mana (reduced through training). 
	
Battle Hymn has a small chance to cause inspirations that will further boost combat abilities. 
	
Use the skill to activate or deactivate the ability.</TM_BattleHymn.description>

	<TM_BardTraining.label>Bard Training</TM_BardTraining.label>

	<TM_BardTraining.description>Hone the skills of a bard by undergoing training in performing arts, comedy, socializing, and inspiration. Each level will change the bard's trait to reflect their skill level.
	
Ranks:
Entertainer: Social impact +10%, Negotiation +20%, Trade +10%,
Pain threshold -10%, carrying capacity -10, work speed -10%

Performer: Social impact +20%, Negotiation +30%, Trade +15%,
Pain threshold -12%, carrying capacity -15, work speed -12%

Minstrel: Social impact +30%, Negotiation +35%, Trade +20%,
Pain threshold -14%, carrying capacity -18, work speed -14%

Bard: Social impact +35%, Negotiation +40%, Trade +25%,
Pain threshold -15%, carrying capacity -20, work speed -15%</TM_BardTraining.description>

	<TM_Lullaby_III.label>Lullaby</TM_Lullaby_III.label>

	<TM_Lullaby_III.description>Projects an emotionally soothing wave that washes away concerns and consciousness that can put any creatures in the target area to sleep.</TM_Lullaby_III.description>

</LanguageData>
