<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<TM_FightersFocus.label>Fighters Focus</TM_FightersFocus.label>

	<TM_FightersFocus.description>Activates or deactivates the sustained combat skill Fighters Focus - increases mental break threshold by 5% and pain threshold by 20%. Requires 15 Stamina to sustain.</TM_FightersFocus.description>

	<TM_BurningFury.label>Burning Fury</TM_BurningFury.label>

	<TM_BurningFury.description>Activates or deactivates the sustained combat skill Burning Fury.
	
Burning Fury causes periodic burning damage to nearby enemies as well as the caster. It also cauterizes bleeding wounds and applies a combat enhancement on the caster.

Burning Fury:
Movement +10%
Breathing +40%
Blood pumping +40%
Pain threshold +40%
Armor (Heat) +100%

While active, the caster cannot be staggered and will reduce all incoming damage by 35%.

This ability actively consumes stamina, and will automatically cancel once the caster's stamina reaches 0.</TM_BurningFury.description>

	<TM_ThickSkin.label>Thick Skin</TM_ThickSkin.label>

	<TM_ThickSkin.description>Activates or deactivates the sustained combat skill Thick Skin - increases all armor values by 10% and improves temperature thresholds slightly. Requires 30 Stamina to sustain and reduces stamina regeneration by 15%.</TM_ThickSkin.description>

	<TM_HeavyBlow.label>Heavy Blow</TM_HeavyBlow.label>

	<TM_HeavyBlow.description>Activates or deactivates the sustained combat skill Heavy Blow - increases damage of all attacks by 20%. Requires 30 Stamina to sustain.</TM_HeavyBlow.description>

	<TM_GearRepair.label>Gear Repair</TM_GearRepair.label>

	<TM_GearRepair.description>Activates or deactivates the sustained combat skill Gear Repair - slowly repairs equipped apparel and weapons. Requires 20 Stamina to sustain.</TM_GearRepair.description>

	<TM_InnerHealing.label>Inner Healing</TM_InnerHealing.label>

	<TM_InnerHealing.description>Activates or deactivates the sustained combat skill Inner Healing - sacrifices physical energy to increase healing rate and disease immunity. Requires 10 Stamina to sustain.</TM_InnerHealing.description>

	<TM_StrongBack.label>Strong Back</TM_StrongBack.label>

	<TM_StrongBack.description>Activates or deactivates the sustained combat skill Strong Back - increases carry capacity by 40 and inventory capacity by 50% but causes a 10% increase in exhaustion rate. Requires 20 Stamina to sustain.</TM_StrongBack.description>

</LanguageData>
