<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<TM_Transpose.label>Transpose</TM_Transpose.label>

	<TM_Transpose.description>Swap places with a target pawn. The faceless and the target will be disoriented following transposition. The faceless will gain reversal for a short period.
Cast time: .8s
Range: 40
Cooldown: 15</TM_Transpose.description>

	<TM_Transpose_I.label>Transpose I</TM_Transpose_I.label>

	<TM_Transpose_I.description>Swap places with a target pawn. The faceless and the target will be disoriented following transposition. The faceless will gain reversal for a short period.
Cast time: .6s
Range: 44
Cooldown: 13</TM_Transpose_I.description>

	<TM_Possess.label>Possess</TM_Possess.label>

	<TM_Possess.description>Like a puppet master, the faceless applies of the mind and body to cause extreme self-doubt on a target pawn - allowing them to control their target through mental suggestion and coercion. 
		
Nearby enemies are unlikely to immediately detect the possession unless they see suspicious activity. If detected, neutral and friendly factions will consider aggressive actions from a possessed pawn as an act of hostility.

Only creatures with a human-like mind capable of self-doubt can be possessed.</TM_Possess.description>

	<TM_Reversal.label>Reversal</TM_Reversal.label>

	<TM_Reversal.description>Reverses the kinetic energy of all melee and projectile attacks for a brief period. The faceless will take no damage from these attacks. Direct application and explosive attacks cannot be reversed.</TM_Reversal.description>

	<TM_Transpose_II.label>Transpose II</TM_Transpose_II.label>

	<TM_Transpose_II.description>Swap places with a target pawn. The faceless and the target will be disoriented following transposition. The faceless will gain reversal for a short period.
Cast time: .4s
Range: 47
Cooldown: 11</TM_Transpose_II.description>

	<TM_Mimic.label>Mimic</TM_Mimic.label>

	<TM_Mimic.description>The faceless copies a random ability from a mage or fighter. Only one ability may be stored at a time. The ability is retained after use; reusing Mimic will replace the stored ability.</TM_Mimic.description>

	<TM_Disguise.label>Deception</TM_Disguise.label>

	<TM_Disguise.description>The faceless manipulates light and motion to make their form appear meaningless to any observer; on a subconscious level, any observer will cognitively dismiss the faceless as an unimportant, harmless object, essentially making the faceless invisible.
	
Disguise will not fool any pawn that already sees the faceless as a threat.</TM_Disguise.description>

	<TM_Transpose_III.label>Transpose III</TM_Transpose_III.label>

	<TM_Transpose_III.description>Swap places with a target pawn. The faceless and the target will be disoriented following transposition. The faceless will gain reversal for a short period.
Cast time: .2s
Range: 50
Cooldown: 9</TM_Transpose_III.description>

</LanguageData>
